<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects | Yunpeng Zhao</title>
    <link>https://RedPisa.github.io/project/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://RedPisa.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projects</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://RedPisa.github.io/media/icon_hu736bd6c5da1b5fcc9079d13e6324e18a_493277_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://RedPisa.github.io/project/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bachelor Thesis</title>
      <link>https://RedPisa.github.io/project/bachelor-thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://RedPisa.github.io/project/bachelor-thesis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bachelor Thesis:&lt;/strong&gt; A Weakly-Supervised Image Classification Framework Based on Graph Convolutional Networks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A feasible framework based on graph convolutional networks (GCN) for weakly supervised image classification is built, including deep feature extraction, graph construction, and weakly supervised graph convolutional networks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Considering a single image as a vertex, autoencoder and SimCLR are employed to extract discriminative node features. Then two similarity-based strategies for adjacency matrix construction are designed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Initial residual connection and identity mapping methods are injected into SelfSAGCN, a model for weakly-supervised node classification, to ease the over-smoothing problem and improve its performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The framework achieves better performance on CIFAR-10 and STL-10 datasets, compared with existing weakly-supervised image classification models based on GCNs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Punctate Highlight Removal for Microscopic Images Based on Pix2pixHD</title>
      <link>https://RedPisa.github.io/project/highlights/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://RedPisa.github.io/project/highlights/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Punctate Highlight Removal for Microscopic Images Based on Pix2pixHD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designed a framework based on pix2pixHD to remove punctate highlights in microscopic images.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proposed a microscopic image dataset consisting of 7500 microscopic images in the size of 256×256 with punctate highlights and 7500 corresponding images without highlights.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We combine the traditional method of highlight removal with the deep learning model pix2pixHD. The traditional method is employed to generate a binary mask indicating the approximate highlight area as the priori information. Then the mask is concatenated with the 3-channel highlighted microscopic image as the input of the generator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our model is trained by calculating a weighted GAN loss to achieve a better performance of highlight removal. Specifically, we simply increase the weight of loss of highlighted pixels according to the binary mask.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
